Hey you
뭘 보니?
내가 좀 Sexy Sexy 반했니
Ye you
뭐 하니?
너도 내 Kiss Kiss 원하니
월 화 수 목 금 토 일 미모가 쉬지를 않네
머리부터 발끝까지 눈부셔
빛이 나네
Oh 저기 언니야들
내 Fashion을 따라 하네
아름다운 여자의 하루는
다 아름답네
이 Party에 준비된
Birthday cake
태어나서 감사해 Every day
I don’t need them
그래 내가 봐도 난
퀸카 I’m hot
My boob and booty is hot
Spotlight 날 봐
I’m a star star star
퀸카 I’m the top
I’m twerking on the runway
I am a 퀸카
You wanna be the 퀸카
I’m a 퀸카
I’m a I’m a I’m a 퀸카
(Take a photo)
I’m a 퀸카
I’m a I’m a I’m a 퀸카
Look so cool
look so sexy
like Kim Kardashian
Look so cute
look so pretty like Ariana
I wanna with you 뽀뽀
I wanna with you 포옹
자꾸 예뻐져 거울 속 너어~
이 Party에 준비된
Champagne
태어난 걸 축하해 Every day
I don’t need them
그래 내가 봐도 난
퀸카 I’m hot
My boob and booty is hot
Spotlight 날 봐
I’m a star star star
퀸카 I’m the top
I’m twerking on the runway
I am a 퀸카
You wanna be the 퀸카
I’m a 퀸카
I’m a I’m a I’m a 퀸카
(Take a photo)
I’m a 퀸카
I’m a I’m a I’m a 퀸카
아무거나 걸친 Girl
퀸카카카
마르거나 살찐 Girl
자신감 넘치는 Girl
퀸카카카
I am a 퀸카
You wanna be the 퀸카